JOHN GARZON

100 Golden Isles Dr. Hallandale, FL 33009 954 - 681 - 3241

gajohn511@gmail.com

https://whispering-wildwood-43957.herokuapp.com/

SUMMARY

Software Developer with 5+ years experience in ASP.Net / SQL / HTML / CSS / JavaScript. I have experienced with telerik controls 3+ years, and experienced using frameworks such as CSS Bootstrap, JQuery, and Vuejs. I love programming, team oriented environments, and fun bosses. Seeking a team oriented developer position.

Node skills: MongoDB / NodeJS / NPM / Git / Grunt

ASPNET skills: MVC 4, LINQ, VS 2008+, Team Foundation, .Net 4.0+, SQL Server 2008+, T-SQL

EXPERIENCE

Broadway Across America Pompano FL — *Software Engineer*

Feb 2014 - Dec 2016

Engineer to our ticket sales RESTful web services, consumed by the public domain, using .net & Restful. Team member to the front-end ninjas, developed an in-house admin application for ticket sales and administration, using full stack and employing Agil. Keeping our applications up to date, version pushes, enhancements, and bug fixes, with a lot of front-end development: CSS bootstrap 3.5 / jquery / json / ajax.

http://www.broadway.com

First Service Residential Inc. Dania Beach FL — Software Developer

Nov 2008 - Feb 2014

I was solely responsible of the legacy iteration of Connect titled Connect3 when I first came on board, developed in ASP and MySQL, supporting and maintenance of the system for 3+ years. Also a developer to our SaaS application - FSR Community website, developed in .NET, specialized in bug fixes, enhancement, and QA. I was then part of the team to help develop and migrate connect 3 to Connect4 (next iteration enterprise system SaaS software developed in .net 4.0 with telerik) to production, following all phases of SDLC. http://fsrsouth.myconnect.cc (Connect 4) https://dcmetro.fsrconnect.com

EDUCATION

F.I.U Miami FL — Bachelors of Information Technology

Sep 2004 - May 2008

Pace University, New York NY—M.I.S. Sep 2000 - Jun 2003